motors.co.uk 2019-06-01

# Privacy

**Privacy Policy**

We respect your privacy and we are committed to protecting it and to complying with applicable data protection and privacy laws. We have provided this Policy statement to help you understand how we collect, use and protect your personal information when you visit Motors.co.uk.

Please note that this Policy may change from time to time and, if it does, the latest version will always be available on the Site.

  1. **Who we are**

Motors.co.uk Ltd is the data controller in respect of any personal information to which this privacy policy applies. You can contact us at:

Motors.co.uk Head Office

127 Olympic Avenue

Milton Park

Abingdon

Oxfordshire

OX14 4SA

Or via email: [privacy@motors.co.uk](mailto:privacy@motors.co.uk)

References in this privacy policy to the Motors.co.uk Network should be taken as referring to the following partner websites. This list may change from time to time but the most up to date list will be displayed here:

  * Autoclubsinternational.com
  * Autoexpress.co.uk
  * Autovillage.co.uk
  * Carmagazine.co.uk
  * Carmony.co.uk
  * Carmoney.co.uk
  * Carsite.co.uk
  * Carsource.co.uk
  * Cheapmotors.co.uk
  * Confused.com
  * Desperateseller.co.uk
  * Drive24.co.uk
  * Honestjohn.co.uk
  * Motoring.co.uk
  * Motorway.co.uk
  * Scottishmotors.com
  * Parkers.co.uk
  * Petrolprices.com
  * Preloved.co.uk
  * Raccars.co.uk
  * Usedcarexpert.co.uk
  * Vansa2z.com

  2. **What we do with your personal information**

Motors.co.uk Ltd collects the following personal information about you and uses it for the following purposes:

1) When you sign up for a My Garage account or otherwise want to buy or sell a vehicle using the Motors.co.uk website, we collect your email address, name, postcode and mobile number. We use this information for the purposes of setting up and administering your account on Motors.co.uk. We also use your mobile number as a means of verification when you sell cars using the motors.co.uk website

2) If you are a dealer, whether a sole trader or other form of company, we also collect amongst other things postal addresses, VAT Number, Company Number, names of directors, owners or partners of the business and driver license number. We collect this information to set up and administer your Motors.co.uk account.

3) When you express interest in a vehicle, such as requesting an appointment to view or test drive the vehicle, we will share your contact details with the dealer so they can contact you to deal with such requests.

4) We use IP addresses for three reasons:

  1. To determine whether activity on our domains has been carried out by human activity as opposed to bot or crawler activity.
  2. For research purposes in order to help us understand consumer activity and search trends on our network.
  3. To help determine your location to make searching for vehicles more effective.

5) We use cookies on our domains to collect information about how and what you browse our domains and use this data to create audiences for marketing purposes. For more information about cookies, how we use them, and how to opt out please refer to our Cookies section (5).

6) We retain a log of your correspondence with us including emails, online chat sessions and telephone calls. We retain any personal data contained within these communications for the purposes of providing an audit trail of your interactions with us. We also provide access to this information to our dealers for quality control and monitoring purposes. Recordings of telephone calls are retained for 90 days and recordings of emails are retained for 2 years.

7) Where you inquire about or purchase a vehicle from a dealer, we may provide additional information to that dealer. We provide details of the postcode you supply and details of the vehicle searches and results to the dealer. This is provided to allow dealers to monitor through traffic from Motors.co.uk and the Motors.co.uk Network and monitor how many sales are generated using the Motors.co.uk website and Motors.co.uk Network.

**2.1 Grounds on which we process your personal data**

Motors.co.uk Ltd processes your personal information on the following grounds:

1)  **Performance of a contract**

Motors.co.uk provides a service where we connect buyers and sellers of vehicles. Where you use motors.co.uk to buy or sell a vehicle whether as a dealer or private individual, you are entering into a contract with Motors.co.uk Ltd in relation to the use of our service. We process the personal data collected during the transaction process in order to provide this service by storing and exchanging this data with the buyer and seller.

2)  **Consent**

Where we process your personal data for direct marketing purposes is based on us having contained valid opt in consent from you to do so.

You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time though this does not affect the lawfulness of the processing of your personal information prior to that withdrawal. You can withdraw your consent by contacting us at [privacy@motors.co.uk](mailto:privacy@motors.co.uk).

3)  **Legitimate Interests**

Where it is not necessary for us to process personal data for the performance of our contract with you, such as the correspondence logs, then this personal data is processed on the basis of Motors.co.uk or the third party to whom we provide the data pursuing legitimate business interests.

It is in our legitimate interest to maintain audit logs of communications between Motors.co.uk and buyers and sellers of vehicles via Motors.co.uk. This is to assist in dispute resolution, for quality monitoring purposes and in order for us to demonstrate the value of our service to our clients.

Processing undertaken for any other purpose set out in section 2 above which has not otherwise been specifically dealt with here is processed on the basis of legitimate interests. It is in the legitimate interests of Motors.co.uk to understand the activities of those who use our products and services, including websites, to ensure that activity is being undertaken is legitimate, i.e.it is being undertaken by natural persons instead of bots.

  3. **Disclosures and Transfers**

Motors.co.uk Ltd will or may pass your personal information on to the following recipients or categories of recipients:

  * Staff of Motors.co.uk Ltd or staff members of those who process personal data on behalf of Motors.co.uk Ltd as set out in this section.
  * We may occasionally use data processors (as set out below) who are located outside of the European Union.
  * We share dealer contact information contained within advertisements listed on our website with the Motors.co.uk network.
  * Dealers from whom you wish to buy a vehicle.

  4. **Your rights in relation to your personal information**

You have the following rights in relation to the personal information Motors.co.uk Ltd processes relating to you. Where you exercise these rights, Motors.co.uk Ltd will provide information to you as to what action has been taken, if any, within 30 calendar days of receipt of your request. Where no action has been taken, Motors.co.uk Ltd will explain our reasons why.

Taking into account the complexity and number of requests, it may take Motors.co.uk Ltd up to 90 calendar days to respond to your request. Where Motors.co.uk Ltd intends to extend the deadline for responding, you will be informed within 30 calendar days of receipt of your request.

**4.1 Right of Access**

You have the right to request access to the personal information that Motors.co.uk Ltd hold about you.

**4.2 Rights in relation to inaccurate personal information**

Where personal information that Motors.co.uk Ltd holds about you is inaccurate, you have the right to request that those inaccuracies are rectified. Taking into account the purposes for which the personal information is processed, you also have the right to have incomplete personal information about you completed.

**4.3 Right to erasure**

In certain limited circumstances, you have the right to request that Motors.co.uk Ltd erase personal information relating to you that Motors.co.uk Ltd holds. This right only applies if any one of the following circumstances applies:

  * Where Motors.co.uk Ltd no longer require the personal information for the purpose(s) for which it was obtained or otherwise used.
  * Where the processing is based on your consent, that consent has been withdrawn and there is no other legal ground for processing.
  * Where you have exercised your right to object to the processing and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing.
  * Where you have exercised your right to object to the use of your personal information for direct marketing purposes.
  * Where the personal information has been unlawfully processed.
  * Where Motors.co.uk Ltd are required to erase the personal information in order to comply with a legal obligation.

The right does not apply where the processing of your personal information is necessary:

  * For compliance with a legal obligation requiring Motors.co.uk Ltd to process your personal information or where the processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest
  * For the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

**4.4 Right to restriction of processing**

You have the right to request that Motors.co.uk Ltd restrict the processing of your personal information in the following circumstances:

  * Where you have contested the accuracy of the personal information. In this case the processing of the personal information will be restricted for a period which enables Motors.co.uk Ltd to verify the accuracy of the personal information in question.
  * Where the processing of the personal information is unlawful and you have objected to the information being erased and have instead requested the restriction of its use.
  * Where Motors.co.uk Ltd no longer needs the personal information for the purposes set out in part 2 above but you require them for establishing, exercising or defending legal claims.
  * Where you have objected to the processing of your personal information as set out in section 3.6.1 below. In this case, processing of your personal information will be restricted pending verification of whether our legitimate grounds for continuing to process your personal information override your grounds for objecting.

Where processing of your personal information is restricted for any of the reasons above Motors.co.uk Ltd will not process it, with the exception of storage, unless:

  * You have provided your consent,
  * For the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims,
  * For the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person, or
  * For reasons of important public interest.

Where Motors.co.uk Ltd have agreed to restrict the processing of your personal information, we will write to you to inform you that we will be lifting that restriction prior to doing so.

**4.5 Right to data portability**

This right only applies in the following circumstances:

  * Where the personal information in question consists of information you have provided to Motors.co.uk Ltd,
  * Where the grounds for processing the personal information stated in section 2 above are consent, explicit consent or for the performance of a contract or to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract, and
  * The processing of the personal information is carried via automated means.

Where this right applies, you have the right to receive your personal information in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format. You also have the right to transmit that information to another data controller or, where possible, directly from Motors.co.uk Ltd to another controller.

**4.6 Right to object to processing**

You have the following rights in relation to objecting to the processing of your personal information by Motors.co.uk Ltd:

  * You have the right to object at any time, on grounds relating to your particular situation, to the processing, and
  * The right to object specifically to the processing of your personal information for direct marketing purposes.

**4.6.1 Right to object to processing**

You have the right to object to the processing of your personal information at any time, on grounds relating to your particular situation. This only applies where the grounds for processing are:

  * The processing is necessary for the purposes of legitimate interests pursued by the data controller or by a third party, or
  * Processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest

**4.6.2 Right to object to processing for the purposes of direct marketing**

You have the right to object specifically to the processing of your personal information for the purposes of direct marketing. If you object to the processing of your personal information in this way, then Motors.co.uk Ltd will no longer process it for that purpose.

**4.7**   **Rights in relation to automated decision making & profiling**

You have the right not to be subjected to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which would legally affect you or significantly affect you. However, this right will not apply if the decision:

  * Is necessary for the entering into, or performance of, a contract between you and Motors.co.uk Ltd
  * Is authorised by or under any law to which Motors.co.uk Ltd is subject, or
  * Is based on your explicit consent.

**4.8 Right to complain to the Information Commissioner's Office**

Where you believe that Motors.co.uk Ltd has failed to properly comply with its obligations in respect of your personal information, including your rights as set out in section 3.1-3.7 above, you can complain to the Information Commissioner.

The Information Commissioner's Office address is:

The Information Commissioner's Office   
Wycliffe House   
Water Lane   
Wilmslow   
Cheshire   
SK9 5AF

You can find more information about their role and how to submit a complaint on their website: [www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/).

  5. **Cookies**

As set out in section 2 above, a cookie is a small piece of data that is sent from our web server to your browser, which is saved on the hard drive of your computer, smartphone or other device.

A cookie cannot:

  * Read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites;
  * Damage your system;
  * Run programmes on your computer; or
  * Deliver viruses.

**5.1**   **Why do we use Cookies?**

The cookies used on the Site are broken into  **five**  categories and are explained below in this clause 6.1 with options to opt out of all or selected cookies.

**5.2**   **Essential Site Cookies**

These cookies allow you to use essential features of our Site. The essential features of our Site require the use of certain cookies so that we can remember your postcode and what is in your shortlist whilst you continue to browse our Site and/or navigate to different pages of the Site during your browsing session. We are also able to identify you as being logged in to the Site and ensure that you are able to access the appropriate features on our Site.

Below is a list of the essential cookies that we use on the Site:

**Name**

| 

**Type and Duration**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
motSeaPanUseCar

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Enabling searches for used cars to be saved improving user experience on the Site.  
  
motSeaPanUseVan

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Enabling searches for used vans to be saved improving user experience on the Site.  
  
motSeaPanBas

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Remembers users basic data like postcode to enable improved user experience and faster searches.  
  
motSeaPanCarDea

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Enabling searches for car dealers to be saved improving user experience on the Site.  
  
motSeaPanVanDea

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Enabling searches for van dealers to be saved improving user experience on the Site.  
  
motSeaPanNewCar

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Enabling searches for new cars to be saved improving user experience on the Site.  
  
motSeaPanNewVan

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Enabling searches for new vans to be saved improving user experience on the Site.  
  
motSeaPanCarDeaSto

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Enabling searches for car dealer stock to be saved improving user experience on the Site.  
  
motSeaPanVanDeaSto

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Enabling searches for van dealer stock to be saved improving user experience on the Site.  
  
motbreadcrumbs

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Ensuring a user's journey has the best experience by enabling a breadcrumb of where the users been.  
  
motorsVehicleShortList

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

This gives the user access to the shortlist feature enabling them to access vehicles they want to store for future reference.  
  
motPosPro

| 

Persistent, 1 Day

| 

Once a user enters a page we want to ensure the user has the best experience on the site so we ask them to submit location after 5 detail page views.  
  
motorsSEO

| 

Persistent, 1 Day

| 

Once a user enters a page we want to ensure the user has the best experience on the site so we ask them to submit location after 5 detail page views.  
  
motwmwcusdat

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Customer details for What's Mine Worth  
  
motorsWMWVRM

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Allows us to carry data back to Private Seller after a valuation  
  
motorsWMWMileage

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Allows us to carry data back to Private Seller after a valuation  
  
motPendingAction

| 

Persistent, 1 Day

| 

If an event requires a login  
  
motNigOwlDat

| 

Persistent, 1 Day

| 

Allows us to pre-populate Night Owl email form on car details pages  
  
ASP.NET_SessionId

| 

Session

| 

Session ID information for .NET which allows a better browsing experience  
  
SessionID

| 

Session

| 

Session ID. Non-personally identifiable for consistent experience  
  
MSPreferredCulture

| 

Session

| 

For Kentico Locale content management system (New, Reviews, etc)  
  
accfirstname

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Logged in user first name for My Garage functionality  
  
acclastname

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Logged in user last name  
  
motorsSearchGuid

| 

Persistent, 30 Days

| 

Search Identifier for better browsing experience  
  
motorsCookieMsg

| 

100 Days

| 

We show a cookie message to users explaining that we use them to optimise the Site. This stores if they want this message to be hidden  
  
motPerVeh

| 

Persistent, 30 days

| 

Enabling the site to remember the last viewed vehicle  
  
motVehDetNav

| 

Persistent, 1 day

| 

Contains vehicleId in order to enable the vehicle details navigation slider  
  
superchargerDisplayState

| 

Persistent, 3 Days

| 

Records user preference for displaying our Supercharger search results  
  
motDev

| 

Persistent, 365 Days

| 

This is the device id which gives the device that the user is using a unique id so that we can if required understand activity from a device.  
  
motDevFirstAccess

| 

Persistent, 365 Days

| 

The date at which a device first accessed the site.  
  
motFeatureVersion

| 

Session

| 

Stores the version of a feature on the site.  
  
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that or to notify you each time a cookie is set.

Visiting [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) will provide information on settings within your browser as well as other useful information on cookies.

Below are links to most used browsers with information for blocking cookies, however, be mindful that if you use multiple browsers you will have to undertake this process on each browser and blocking these essential Site cookies will result in a limited experience of the site:

**5.3**   **Anonymous Visit Counting Cookie**

This cookie allows a third party to collect anonymous visitor information to give a view of the total site traffic and other metrics like page views to compare with competitor websites.

**Name**

| 

**Type and Duration**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
Comscore/ .scorecardsearch.com/ UID

| 

Persistent, 2 Years

| 

Measure site visit and page view metrics  
  
Opt out

| 

<http://www.scorecardresearch.com/preferences.aspx>  
  
**5.4 Analytics and Optimisation Cookies**

These cookies are used to measure website performance, monitor engagement and run experiments to improve user experience of the Site. You can opt-out of each service by following the link in the opt-out section of the table below:

**Name**

| 

**Type and Duration**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**Google Analytics**  
  
_utma

| 

Persistent

| 

Keeps track of the number of times a visitor has been to the site to measure things like returning visitor rate  
  
_utmb & _utmc

| 

Session & 30 mins

| 

Used to measure length of visit  
  
Conductrics

| 

Depends on the length of the experiment but typically no more than 30 days.

| 

Used to determine a user's inclusion in an experiment and the expiry of experiments a user has been included in.  
  
Wisepops

|  | 

Used to show Motors.co.uk offers and products.  
  
_utmz

| 

Persistent, 180 days

| 

Identifies where the user came from before visiting the Site and collects details such as keyword or campaign  
  
**Google Optimise**  
  
_gaexp

| 

Depends on the length of the experiment but typically 90 days.

| 

Used to determine a user's inclusion in an experiment and the expiry of experiments a user has been included in  
  
**Opt out**

| 

<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>  
  
**Hotjar**  
  
_hjClosedSurveyInvites

| 

This cookie is set once a visitor interacts with a Survey invitation modal popup. It is used to ensure that the same invite does not re-appear if it has already been shown.  
  
_hjDonePolls

| 

This cookie is set once a visitor completes a poll using the Feedback Poll widget. It is used to ensure that the same poll does not re-appear if it has already been filled in.  
  
_hjMinimizedPolls

| 

This cookie is set once a visitor minimizes a Feedback Poll widget. It is used to ensure that the widget stays minimizes when the visitor navigates through your site.  
  
_hjDoneTestersWidgets

| 

This cookie is set once a visitor submits their information in the Recruit User Testers widget. It is used to ensure that the same form does not re-appear if it has already been filled in.  
  
_hjMinimizedTestersWidgets

| 

This cookie is set once a visitor minimizes a Recruit User Testers widget. It is used to ensure that the widget stays minimizes when the visitor navigates through your site.  
  
_hjDoneSurveys

| 

This cookie is set once a visitor completes a survey. It is used to only load the survey content if the visitor hasn't completed the survey yet.  
  
_hjIncludedInSample

| 

This session cookie is set to let Hotjar know whether that visitor is included in the sample which is used to generate funnels.  
  
**Opt out**

| 

<https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out>  
  
**5.5 Adserving Cookies**

These cookies are used to deliver the targeted ads that appear on the Site We sell adspace direct to advertisers, our partner, Bauer Media, sells adspace on our Site (on our behalf) to third parties and we also use third party adserving technology that enables the adservers customers to serve ad inventory on our Site based on cookie information.

For a list of the adserving cookies used on the Site and to opt out for each please see the list of providers below:

**Name**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---  
  
**Google DoubleClick for Publishers**  
  
_gads

| 

Used to serve adverts based on your previous browsing behaviour  
  
**Opt out**

| 

<https://support.google.com/dfp_premium/answer/2839090?hl=en>  
  
**OpenX**

| 

Technology which allows advertisers to serve targeted adverts to you based on your browser behaviour  
  
**Opt out**

| 

<https://www.openx.com/legal/interest-based-advertising/>  
  
**5.6 Retargeting & Audience Cookies**

We use various technologies to collect and target users based on cookies. Cookies collect information on user engagement. Various engagements are added together to build audience lists which are then used to show targeted ads to users on third party sites. These audiences are used by us on the behalf of ourselves (Motors.co.uk) and customers (e.g. car dealers and car finance providers).

The platforms, and cookies used for this are listed below with links to opt out pages:

**Name**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---  
  
**Criteo**  
  
tracking pixel

| 

Criteo use a tracking pixel as well as multiple cookies. These cookies keep information such as which pages you viewed and certain other parameters in order to provide more relevant advertisements to our users.  
  
acdc

| 

This cookie keeps track of any parameters that are passed by the site, such as, for example, whether you are using a phone, tablet or desktop, whether you are a new customer, when you arrive and leave the site. It is used for optimising campaign performance.  
  
eid

| 

This cookie is an external identifier that informs publisher networks (i.e. the sites that host the advertisements) who the advertiser is.  
  
evt

| 

This cookie contains information about the last page visited. It is used to retarget advertising.  
  
opt

| 

This cookie allows you to opt out of Criteo advertisers or publishers (in other words, not to see an advertisement any more). Criteo may continue to tracking you in respect of other advertisers/publishers.  
  
optout

| 

This cookie allows you to allows you to opt out of some of Criteo's services.  
  
r.ack

| 

This cookie is used to confirm that you have accepted cookies.  
  
udc

| 

This cookie contains the list of publishers with positive campaign performance based on your behaviours, to improve the performance on the tagging and detagging operations.  
  
uic

| 

This cookie allows Criteo to measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign based on your browsing history.  
  
uid

| 

This cookie sets an internal ID personalised to the user.  
  
zdi

| 

This cookie counts the number of times you are shown an impression on a  
  
Opt out

| 

<http://www.criteo.com/deactivate-criteo-banners/>  
  
Google DoubleClick, Analytics and Adwords  
  
Cookie info: <http://www.google.co.uk/policies/technologies/types/>  
  
Motors.co.uk uses audiences created using Google Analytics cookie data to buy ad inventory through Google DoubleClick  
  
Adwords Conversion tracking

| 

Motors.co.uk uses Google Adwords to build audiences. These audiences are used to buy relevant ad inventory to target users on third party sites.  
  
Adwords Remarketing

| 

Motors.co.uk uses audiences created using Google Adwords cookie data to buy ad inventory through Google DoubleClick  
  
**Opt out**

| 

<https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/>  
  
**Facebook**

| 

Motors.co.uk uses Facebook to buy ads to target users based on browsing behaviour on Motors.co.uk  
  
**Opt out**

| 

<https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>  
  
**Speedshift Media**

| 

Motors.co.uk uses SSM to build dynamic vehicle ads based on user behaviour on Motors.co.uk  
  
**Opt out**

| 

<http://www.speedshiftmedia.com/about/user-choices>  
  
**Captify**

| 

Captify collects ANONYMOUS audience data from Motors.co.uk to sell to 3rd party advertisers  
  
**Opt out**

| 

<http://www.captify.co.uk/privacy-policy/>  
  
**Sirdata**

| 

Sirdata collects ANONYMOUS audience data from Motors.co.uk to sell to 3rd party advertisers  
  
**Opt out**

| 

<https://www.sirdata.com/optout/>  
  
**RTB**

| 

Tracking pixel Criteo use a tracking pixel as well as multiple cookies. These cookies keep information such as which pages you viewed and certain other parameters in order to provide more relevant advertisements to our users.  
  
**Opt out**

| 

<https://www.rtbhouse.com/optout-page/>  
  
**ROKT**

| 

ROKT use cookies to show offers to our users.  
  
**Opt out**

| 

To opt out of this please follow the link within the email that you receive from them.  
  
**5.7 Set 3rd Party Cookie Preference**

We ask for your consent to set cookies when you first visit the site. You can set preferences for each provider using the opt out links in the tables above, or to update your choices at any time [click here](http://content.wordpress.motors.co.uk/). Additionally you can use the [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) or [Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/) website to set your preferences for cookies that may be found for these and other sites.

**5.8 How Google products use cookies**

For a detailed description of how Google use cookies in advertising visit [Google Privacy Terms page.](http://www.google.co.uk/policies/technologies/ads/) Google have given the option for you to opt out of ads that have been served based on your usage of Google products. For further information on how [Google uses data](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/) or to opt out of ads based on your interests visit [Control your Google ads page.](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads)

**5.9 What about Hyperlinks?**

The Site may sometimes contain hyperlinks to websites owned and operated by third parties. These third party websites have their own privacy policies (including cookies) and we urge you to review them. They will govern the use of any personal information you submit or which is collected by cookies whilst visiting these websites. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third party websites and your use of such third party websites is at your own risk.

**5.10 What about Flash Cookies?**

A Flash Cookie is a type of cookie which is collected via Adobe Flash Player, and is a piece of software which you probably have on your device to watch videos or podcasts online. We may use Adobe Flash Player to display video or image content. It may not be possible to block or restrict or block Flash Cookies using your browser settings, however, information on how to control flash play privacy and security settings is available from the Adobe website at: [http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security.](http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security)

**5.11 Who do I contact about Cookies?**

If you have any questions about our use of cookies, please contact us either via the email address or by post at the address set out in clause 3.1.

  6. **Use of Your Personal Information Submitted to Other Websites**

**6.1**  We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other third party websites even if you accessed the third party website using links from the Site or you linked to the Site from a third party website.

**6.2**  We recommend that you check the policy of each website you visit and contact the owner or operator of such website if you have any concerns or questions.

**_December 2017_**

F1
